Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- State of Rhode Island ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01921 95 #95-25 G9849 DHS Fallon Con. OR, 1995-1997 (Box 91, Folder 42)
- State of Rhode Island ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01922 95 #94-113 G9812 DHS C/A New Position, 1995-1998 (Box 91, Folder 43)
- State of Rhode Island ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 02556 95 G1101 FNHP Local 5019 Insuff. Staffg, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 44)
- RI Hospital ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 0649 95 RIH/FNHP One day Suspens. (Box 91, Folder 45)
- Rhode Island Hospital ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01392 95 I.B. Teamsters, Local 251 XXXVIII (Box 91, Folder 46)
- Rhode Island Hospital ARB 1995 and AAA #!! 300 01256 95 FNHP sick time pay (Box 91, Folder 47)
- Rhode Island Hospital ARB 2995 and AAA #11 300 02195 95 Layoff FNHP, Local 5098 Certified RNs, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 48)
- RI Zambarano Hospital ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01649 95 RILDC, Local 1134 Termination, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 49)
- RI Philharmonic Orchestra ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00647 95 American Federation of Musicians (Box 91, Folder 50)
- Shaw's Supermarkets Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 0558 95 Susp. UFCW Local 791 (#948) (Box 91, Folder 51)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00705 95 #865 UFCW Local 791 (Box 91, Folder 52)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00708 95 #897 UFCW, Local 791 Termn. (Box 91, Folder 53)
- Shaw's Supermarkets. Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01915 95 #1020 UFCW, Local 791 OT. (Box 91, Folder 54)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00501 95 UFCW, Local 791 Unjust Suspn., 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 55)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 95 and AAA #11 300 0190 95 Termintn UFCW, Local 791, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 56)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 02224 95 #1039 UFCW, Local 791 Benefits for FT, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 57)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 95 and AAA #11 300 02226 95 #1045 UFCW, Local 791, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 58)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 02227 95 #1029 UFCW Local 791 #1041, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 59)
- Stratford, CT. Board of ED. ARB 95 and AAA #12 390 00204 95 Stratford Education Assn., 1995 (Box 91, Folder 60)
- Supervalu, Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01782 95 I.B. Teamsters, Loc. 42 Bonus day, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Upper Cape Cod Regnl Voc-Tech. SDC and AAA #11 390 01702 95 Filemec Upper Cape Cod Reg. Voc Tech TA, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Department of Defense ARB 1995 and FMCS #95-08910 AFGE, Local 3707 Premium/ Back Pay (Box 92, Folder 3)
- U.S. Immigration & Nat. Service 95 and FMCS $95-18930 OT Reduction AFGE, Local 2076, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- S.D. Warren Company ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00498 95 UPIU, Local 1069 #94-289 Training (Box 92, Folder 5)
- S.D. Warren Company ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01525 95 PPE UPIU. Local 1069 #95245 policy, 1994-1996 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- S.D. Warren Company ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01973 95 Termtn. UPIU, Local 9 P. Leadbetter, 1996-1997 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- City of Warwick, RI ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01379 95 IAFF, Local 2748, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Westerly, Town of, RI ARB 1994 and AAA #11 E 390 0512 95 RILDC, Local 15 Pos. Denial, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Windsor Nursing Home, MA ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 0250 95 Sick Time Hospital Workers Loc 767 and Vacation, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Visiting Nurse Service of ARB 95 and AAA #11300 01684 95 Woonsocket FNHP, Local 5022 Holiday Pay, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- City of Worchester MA ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 02409 94 Worchester Firefighters. Local 1009 (Folder 1 of 2), 1994- 1998 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- City of Worchester MA ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 02409 94 Worchester Firefighters. Local 1009 (Folder 2 of 2), 1994- 1998 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Agreement between City of Worcester and Local 1009 International Association of Firefighters, AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 14)
- Agreement between City of Worcester and Local 1009 International Association of Firefighters, AFL-CIO and Other Related Docs., 1994 (Box 92, Folder 15)
- Agreement between City of Worcester and Local 1009 International Association of Firefighters, AFL-CIO and Related Docs., 1994 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- Marblehead Public Schools Pages 1-131 and 132-224, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Marblehead Public Schools Pages 225-324 and 325-450, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 18)
- Marblehead Public Schools Pages 451-618, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Marblehead Public Schools Pages 619-741 and 742-775, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- Marblehead Public Schools Pages 776-938, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 21)
- Marblehead Public Schools Pages 939-1082, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Marblehead Public Schools Pages 1083-1184 and 1185-1229, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- ARB, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Contract, 1992-1995 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Marblehead, MA School Committee and AAA #11 390 02664 95 Dismiss Ed. Reform Act, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  Contains four photographs
- Marblehead School District AAA Case Mp. 11 390 02664 95, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Marblehead School District AAA Case Mp. 11 390 02664 95, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Marblehead School Committee Marblehead, Massachusetts and The Dismissed Teachers (Folder 1 of 3), 1997 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Marblehead School Committee Marblehead, Massachusetts and The Dismissed Teachers (Folder 2 of 3), 1996 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Marblehead School Committee Marblehead, Massachusetts and The Dismissed Teachers (Folder 3 of 3), 1996 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Atlas Distributing, Inc. ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 0036 96 Truck Drivers Union, Local 170 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Boise Cascade ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01242 96 Upgrades UPIU, Local 900, 1995-1997 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- UPIU Local 900 v. Mead Paper Multiple Grievances- Upgrades AAA #11 300 01232 96, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Boston Edison Company ARB 1996 and Payroll Rep. Staffing UWUA, Local 387 OT and P Gr. #23-1996 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Boston Edison Company and Local 387, Utility Workers Union of America AFLC-CIO, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Town of Bourne, MA ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00832 96 #96-13 Bourne Firefighters Union, 1996-1998 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Brattleboro Retreat ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01865 96 Dischrg BR FNHP, Local 5086, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- University of Bridgeport, CT 1996 and AAA #12 300 00382 96 C. Koret O.P.E.I.U., Local 153 Termination, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Town of Bristol, RI ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 01062 96 Walpol IBPO, Local 304 Calcultn of SL, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Town of Bristol, RI ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 01477 96 #96-12 IBPO, Local 304 6/6/96 memo exp., 1997 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Central Maine Power CO. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 02698 96 #96-51 IBEW, Local 1837 Reo. Doing bu wk, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Central Maine Power Co. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01683 96 #96-19 IBEW, Local 1837 OT and Callouts, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Champion Paper CO. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01094 96 #M6-95- UPIU, Loc. 1188 008 Schedule chg., 1997 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Chinet Company ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-03641 Termination UPIU, Local 449 Keith Wilde Refusal to Work Harrnet, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- City of Clearwater, FL ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-16350-8 CWA Termination, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Termination Hearing, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Agreement between City of Clearwater, Florida and Communications Workers of America Fiscal Years, 1994-1997 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- City of Clearwater, FL ARB 96 and FMCS #96-20501-8 Forced Use Of CWA, Local 3179 Sick Leave, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Comcast Cable Television ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 00234 95 CT Union of Telephone Works. Inc. (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Danbury Hospital ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 00373 96 DH Professional Nurses Assn. Low, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Fonda Group ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01760 96 UPIU, Local 345 #96-07 Discipline, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- City of Fort Lauderdale, FL 1996 and FMCS #96-04514 Fraternal Order of Police L. 31 (Box 94, Folder 15)
- Town of Framingham, MA ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00942 96 IAFF, Local 1652 Improper Transfr, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- Hartford Board of Education 1996 and AAA #12 390 00040 96 #95-023 Hartford FEDN. Of Teachers HPHS (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Hartford Ball Bearing ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 00341 96 GR. #652 United Auto Workers, Local 1187 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Hollingsworth and Vose ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 00023 96 #95-28 UPIU, Local 880 Overtime (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Hollingsworth and Vose ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 00799 96 #506 UPIU, Local 1889 workforce, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1889, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 21)
- Hollingsworth and Vose ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01347 96 #96-8 UPIU, Local 880, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 22)
- City of Hollywood, FL ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-03030-8 AFSCME, Local 2432 Termination, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 23)
- Host Marriott Corp. ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-08887 HERE, Local 355 Termination (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Jackson Memorial Hospital ARB 96 and FMCS #96-23068-8 West Wing Service EES Intl. U, Local #1991, 1997-1999 (Box 94, Folder 25)
- Jackson Memorial Hospital ARB 96 and FMCS #96-22016-8 Service Employees IU, Local 1991 T, 1996-1998 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  Copy of one newspaper in Spanish
- Jacobs Vehicle Equipment CO. 1996 and AAA #12 300 00410 95 BU Work United Auto Workers, Local 379 (Box 94, Folder 27)
- Keebler Company ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 00090 96 IB Teamsters, Local 559 (Box 94, Folder 28)
- City of Lynn, MA ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 02459 96 Lynn Police Assn. Overtime, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 29)
- City of Lynn, MA ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00821 96 Lynn Police Assn. 2-day suspnsn., 1997 (Box 94, Folder 30)
- Monson School Committee ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00668 96 Pay Monson Teachers Assn. of Nurses (Box 94, Folder 31)
- City of Naples, FL ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-11959 AFSCME, Local 2017, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 32)
- Narragansett, RI School Comm. 96 and AAA #11 390 01901 95 ARB NEA Narragansett Biweekly paymts, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 33)
- Narragansett School Comm. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00970 96 NEARI Narragansett, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 34)
- New England Power Company ARB 96 and Gr. #92-2, 95-22, 96-2 Fuel U.W.U.A., Local #464 Brayton Point, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 35)
- New York Suny - Alfred ARB 1996 and OER #96-08-151 United University Professions, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 36)
- State Univ. of NY HSC Buffalo 96 and OER #95-08-386 UUP, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 37)
- Norfolk County Sheriffs Office 96 and AAA #11 390 01508 96 #96-12 County Correctional Officers Assn., 1996 (Box 94, Folder 38)
- NYNEX/ NET Gr. MEDN. MREP 1996 and MREP #113 Pat Fitzmaurice IBEW, Local 2222 Susp. And Termn. (Box 94, Folder 39)
- NYNEX/ NET ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 00241 96 IBEW, Loc. 2322 Final Warning Let., 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 40)
- NYNEX/NET ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01339 91 IBEW, Loc. 2324 Susp. And Letter, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 41)
- NYNEX ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01819 96 IBEW, Local 2320 Harassment, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 42)
- NYNEX/NET ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01376 96 Wage $ IBEW, Loc. 2322 #61-96, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 43)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2322, and NYNEX Vol. I and II, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 44)
- OSRAM Sylvania, Inc. ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-16804-3 Discharge of IBT Local 42 Anderson, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Osram Sylvania, Respondent Vol. I, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Osram Sylvania, Inc. ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-24492-3 Temp. Transfr IBT, Local 42 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- City of Peabody, MA ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00881 96 Peabody Police Benevolent Assn., 1997 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Providence RI School Comm. ARB 96 and AAA #11 390 01976 95 Medical Providence Teachers Union, L. 958, 1996-1997 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- City of Providence, RI ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00894 96 Water Public Service EES, Loc. 1033 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- City of Providence, RI ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 01499 96 Zanfagna RILDC, Local 1033, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- State of Rhode Island ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 01671 96 Termn of RI Council 94 AFSCME A. Gizzareli, 1981-1997 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  A cassette tape discovered in this folder was moved to 6091 AV, box 14, in the media case drawer 16, row b
- State of Rhode Island ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 02052 96 Susp. RI Council 94, AFSCME, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- URI Board of Governors ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 00879 96 URI/PSA/NEARI/ NEA Termination (Box 95, Folder 10)
- URI/ RI BD. Of Gov. for Higher EDN and AAA #11390 01272 96 AAUP Failure to Promote, 1997-1998 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Rhode Island Hospital ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 00457 96 Susp. FNHP, Local 5098, AFT (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Rhode Island Hospital ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 02541 96 FNHP, Local 5098 Rad. Tech. Termn (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 96 and AAA #11 300 02518 95 #1065 UFCW, Local #791, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 96 and Warehouse Wage Rates UFCW, Local 791, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 96 and AAA #11 300 0838 96 #16M OT UFCW, Local 791, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 96 and AAA #11 300 0839 96 #1096 UFCW Local 791, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 96 and AAA #11 300 00844 96 #1101 UFCW, Local 791, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 96 and AAA #11 300 0846 96 #1104 UFCW, Local 791, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 01535 96 #1124 UFCW, Local 791 (Box 95, Folder 20)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 02173 96 #1154 UFCW, Local 791 DIS, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- Shaw's Supermarket, Inc. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 02180 96 #1152 UFCW, Local 791 Termination, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 22)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 02190 96 #1163 UFCW, Local 791 Discharge, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 23)
- NASHUA Telegraph Publishing Co, and ARB 1996 GCIU, Local No. 600M, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 24)
- Tiverton, RI, Town of ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 01959 96 #96-6 IBPO, Local 406 benefits, 1997-1998 (Box 95, Folder 25)
- Torrington Company ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 00101 96 Hours UAW, Local 1645 (Box 95, Folder 26)
- Trinity Hill ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 00065 96 Denial NE Health Care, 1199 of CBA Rights, 1997-1999 (Box 95, Folder 27)
- U.S. Army Corps. Of Engineers 96 and Evaluation NATL. FED. Of Federal EES L. 561, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 28)
- City of Vero Beach, FL ARB 1996 and FMCS #96-00818 IB of Teamsters, Local 769 (Box 95, Folder 29)
- S.D. Warren Company ARB 1996 and AAA #11 300 00242 95 #94-291 UPIU, Local 1060 (Box 95, Folder 30)
- City of Warwick, RI Int. ARB 96 and AAA #11 390 00028 96 Fraternal Order of Police #7, 1996-1997 (Box 95, Folder 31)
- Town of West Warwick ARB 1996 and AAA #11 390 01703 96 illness West Warwick, Loc. 1104. IAFF, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 32)
- WGBH Educational Foundation 1996 and Gr. #95-3 NABET- CWA (Box 95, Folder 33)
- WGBH Educational Foundation 1996 and Gr. #96-2 Secs. 20.3 and 20.4 NABET-CWA, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 34)
- Windham Hospital ARB 1996 and AAA #12 300 0361 96 FEDN. Of WH RNs Denial of timeoff, 1996-1997 (Box 95, Folder 35)
- Algonquin Regional School District and AAA #11 390 02428 96 Algonquin Teachers Assn. Sick Days, 1996-1997 (Box 95, Folder 36)
- Ann and Hope 1997 and AAA #11 426 00038 97 Disc. Chg., 1998 (Box 95, Folder 37)
- American Medical Response of Mass and AAA #11 300 01565 97 Intl. Assn. of EMTS and Paramedics, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 38)
- Atrium Plaza ARB 1997 and AAA #12 300 00201 97 Erosion NE Health Care EES. Union of BU (Box 95, Folder 39)
- Avon. CT. Board of Education 1997 and AAA #12 390 00003 97 NAGE/IBPO Evaluation (Box 95, Folder 40)
- Bell Atlantic GR. MED. 1997 and MREP #128 NE-P97-44 IBEW, Local 2320, 1997-1998 (Box 95, Folder 41)
- Boston Edison Company Direct 1997 and Nuclear Adminstrv Assts. RIF UWUA, Local 387, 1990-1997 (Box 95, Folder 42)
- Bristol Board of ED ARB 1997 and AAA #12 390 00342 97 Bristol Federation of Teachers, 1997-1998 (Box 95, Folder 43)
- Champion Paper Co. and AAA #11 300 00341 97 Hiring UPIU, Local 1188 #1188-4-96-91, 1995-1998 (Box 95, Folder 44)
- 11 300 00341 97 United Paperworkers International Union and Champion Paper Pages 1-179, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- 11 300 00341 97 United Paperworkers International Union and Champion Paper Pages 180-363, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Circuit- Wise Inc. ARB 1997 and AAA #12 300 00357 97 Red Circ United Electrical Workers Loc 299, 1997-1998 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- City of Clearwater, FL ARB 1997 and FMCS #97-15358 Susp. Fraternal Order of Police/ PRA (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Coca-Cola Bottling CO. ARB 1997 and AAA #12 300 00113 97 Warning IBT, Local Union No. 1035 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- State of Connecticut Int. ARB 97 Dept. of Criminal Justice and Connecticut State Employees Assn., 1997-1998 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- State of Connecticut Memorandum No. 97-40 and other Related Docs., 1997 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- The Division of Criminal Justice and Connecticut State Employees Association Police Inspectors Council and Related Docs., 1997- 2001 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- State of Connecticut Division of Criminal Justice and Connecticut Prosecutors and Related Docs., 1997-1999 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- State of Connecticut Interest ARB and P-3A Education Administor Conn. State Employees Assn., 1997-1998 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Division Of Criminal Justice and Connecticut State Employees Association (Inspectors Unit), 1997 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Education Administrators (P-3A) Contract, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Derby Elementary School District and AAA #11 390 00456 97 Health Northeast Kingdom Elem. Teach Asn., 1998 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Fitchburg Gas and Elec. LT. CO. ARB 1997 and Unilat. Remov. Of BUWNE, Loc. No. 340 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Fort Myers Beach Fire Control Dist and FMCS #97-08206 Smoking Policy IAFF, Local 1826, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- O.Z. Gedney Company ARB 1997 and AAA #12 300 00523 97 Rentas USWA Discharge, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Georgetown Public Schools INT ARB 1997 and AAA #11 390 00347 97 Interest Georgetown Education Assn. Pef. (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Hillsborough Area Reg. Trans ARB FMCS #97-18814 Susp. ATU, Local 1593 #97-04-04, 1997-1998 (Box 96, Folder 18)
- H.N.S. Management Co., Inc. ARB and AAA #12 300 00073 97 Amalgamated Transit U. 425 Dischar, 1996-1997 (Box 96, Folder 19)
- CTTRANSIT Rules and Regulations for the Guidance of Maintenance Employees, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Hollingsworth and Vose ARB 1997 and AAA #11 300 00029 97 #5-19 UPIU, Local 1889 Subcontracting, 1997-1998 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Interstate Brands Corp. ARB 1997 and FMCS No. 97-06158-8 I.B. of Teamsters, Local 361 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- James Russell Engineering Works and AAA 11 300 01025 97 ARB 97 UAW, Local 1596 Medical Leave, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Kanzaki Specialty Papers ARB 1997 and AAA #11 300 018878 #N-297 UPIU, Local 708 discipline, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 4)